

New Delhi, India

□ abhishekvasudev7@gmail.com

**** 9582044450

http://abhishekvasudev.github.io https://www.linkedin.com/in/abhishek-vasudev

https://www.codechef.com/users/abhishekv

https://github.com/abhishekvasudev/https://www.facebook.com/abhishek.vasudev.7

About Me

I'm an enthusiast who's passion is coding and software development. I love to do competitive programming. I have hands on experience in software development and team leadership.

My work during internship has been acknowledged by the respective employer. I am a team player.

If you have a role I fit in, please get in touch.

Work Experience

Software Engineer | iOS Developer | July 2018 - Present

Infosys Limited | Navigate your next. & iOS Centre of Excellence | Apple Inc.

Working on Apple Store Application.

<u>Responsibilities</u>: Enhancing developed features, creating new features for the app <u>Technology Stack</u>: Swift, Javascript

Platform/IDE used: XCode, Atom

Enrolled in Fast-Track Batch of Infosys training

Course learned:

- Fundamentals of Swift programming and MACOS Development.
- iOS Development

Freelance Web Developer | October 2017 - January 2018

Pararthya | Sustainable Development & Environment Conservation Society

Worked as Front end Developer.

Projects:

- Developed the company website: http://pararthya.com/
- Worked on SEO for the company website.

Technology Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

Intern: Web Developer | June 2017 - August 2017

Comezo Infotech Pvt. Ltd. | A new age digital platform for school admins, tutors, teachers and students.

Worked as frontend developer.

Projects:

- Developed the company website: http://comezo.in/
- Worked on dynamic content using JavaScript and SEO for the company website.

<u>Technology Stack</u>: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, MySQL

Projects

Apple Store Application (ASA) (Novembor 2018 - Present)

Apple's app for their store representing apple.com. User can buy and track products. User can also book sessions or events happening in nearby Apple Stores

Technology Stack: Swift, JavaScript

My Role: Front end, Responsible for enhancement and maintaining existing features, creating proof of concept for new features.

Park Assist (August 2017 - November 2017)

A mobile application used to help a user by showing nearby parking spaces under the radius of 1 km. The application either takes the current position or the user given address as the search point. The application also provides parking management to the parking owners. The available spaces and booking of a space happen in real time. This is achieved with the use of Firebase.

Technology tack: React Native, CSS, JSON, Firebase, draw.io

My Role: Both Front-end and back-end, prepared PowerPoint Presentation

Teacher Assesssment (February 2017 - Present)

It is a software tool for evaluating teacher performance based on student feedback. Students will get opportunity to grade their teachers so that university can bring improvements in teaching process of faculty. The software evaluates the performance of teacher based on the inputs provided by the students. This will help the new students to know about the teaching faculty and the university to bring improvements in the faculty.

<u>Technology Stack</u>: Java core, JavaFX, MySQL, CSS

My Role: Front-end, Back-end

Quiz (December 2016 - June 2018)

A standalone application for conducting multiple choice based quiz or tests where a user can make test and students can give test.

<u>Technology tack</u>: Java Core, Java Swing <u>My Role</u>: Front-end, Back-end

Achievements

Shortlisted for screening process for the role of Software Developer at Google

Secured first position in graduation batch.

Secured Gold and Silver Medal at National Cyber Olympiad in year 2012 and 2013 respectively.

Skills

Swift Beginner

Java Core Proficient

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript Intermediate

Bootstrap Proficient

Python Beginner

MySQL & Firebase Intermediate

React Native Beginner

PHP & Adobe Photoshop Beginner

Relevent Course Work

Object Oriented Programming

Java Programming

Algorithm Design and Analysis

Data Structure

Software Engineering

Database Management System

Cryptography and Network Security

Education

B.Tech | Information Technology GGSIPU

2014 - 2018

Aggregate: 83.2%

Senior Secondary(XII)

BVB Mehta Vidyalaya 2013 - 2014

Aggregate: 81.40%

Secondary(X)

BVB Mehta Vidyalaya

2011 - 2012 Aggregate: 9.2 CC

Aggregate: 9.2 CGPA (87.40%)

Positions of Responsibility

Team Leader, Smart India Hackathon 2017

Led Team SPI, consisting of 6 members, shortlisted for grand finale

Vice President, Special Projects Initiative(SPI)

Core team member of Special Projects Initiative(SPI) of IT Department of college. Conducted inter section IT department Hackathon.

President, Techedge Club

Elected as President of Techedge Club, Computer Society, at Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan's Mehta Vidyalaya. Conducted Dewang Mehta Memorial Inter School IT Competition.

Event Organizer, Innoviz 2016

Organized 2 events at the annual techno-cultural fest, Innoviz 2016, at college.